Okay, now let's talk about another style.
This style only has one waist.
Let's put this style and the circle together for comparison.
The sleeve in the circle is gone, which means it must have been transferred to the waist.
The armhole in the circle is also gone, which means it has been eliminated.
Let's make the circle in the 3D window.
Press the Shift key.
Let's delete the middle part.
Let's put these two lines together.
Next, let's move this part to this place.
Let's adjust it a little bit.
Delete this point.
Let's check if the two edges are the same.
8.3 and 8.3.
Press the Shift key to select these two edges.
Press the right mouse button.
Rotate the thumb.
At this time, I want to rotate the thumb to the starting point.
So there is already a thumb in this place.
So let's select the edge of the thumb.
The edge of the small piece.
Then we press the left mouse button at the point of the thumb.
Then press the left mouse button to rotate the small piece.
Because the large piece remains unchanged.
It is the front and middle that remain unchanged.
Then rotate my mouse.
Move my mouse.
It is the joint of the袖龙嗓.
Then press the left mouse button.
At this time, we press the left mouse button at the point of the thumb.
Then this style.
We see that it is a little bit below the BP point.
In this case, our shape is a little bit soft.
We put the BP point below.
About 1 to 2 cm.
The number of the thumb should be left.
So the thumb is transferred.
After the transfer, it is not completely finished.
Because our A-thumb has not been removed yet.
The inner line can be deleted at this time.
OK.
In this case, we only need to delete this point.
Left click to select this point.
Then delete.
In this case, the A-thumb after the transfer.
It is already included.
Transferring the袖龙嗓 and the original A-thumb.
Formed a large A-thumb.
OK.
We cut off the other part of the paper sample.
After cutting it off.
We open it in symmetrical.
The area seam line.
OK.
Then we re-seam the side seam.
The gold line is also re-seamed.
After seaming.
Let's check again.
See which place is missing.
Let's look at this.
Because the A-thumb was deleted just now.
So the seam line of the original A-thumb.
Did not put the original A-thumb position.
Hiding the position of the A-thumb.
So we have to pull it up.
OK.
After pulling up.
We are in the 3D window.
We open the 3D window.
Open the arrangement point.
After opening it.
Let's simulate.
OK.
Let's see.
This is transforming into a waist-thumb.
Such a circle.
He was completely the same with the previous A-thumb.